# AMIRHOSSEIN

# **GHASSEMI**

## **CONTACT INFO**

**E-mail** ghassemikamyab@gmail.com

Phone Nr +98 901 6991742

Address Tehran, Iran

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/kamyab-ghassemi

## **ABOUT ME**

 As my professional carrier, I have been working as a front-end developer with React js. i manage my project with scrum I have experience in developing application (with android and rectNative), game(with Unity), webApplication (with ionic), backend server (with javaSpringBoot) and dataBase (Mysql). and also i work with Docker, nginx As a bachelor's student, Now I am working on prediction in cloud service

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **UNITY DEVELOPER**

Sep 2022 - Present

Noyan | Tehran, Iran (Contract)

• Developing a MetaVerse game based on a design in the WEBGL platform

#### **GAME MANAGER**

Aug 2020 - Jan 2022

**Quiz of Kings Game Studio** | Tehran, Iran (Contract)

• Develop game base on design and release MVP

#### **GAME MANAGER**

Sep 2021 -Mar 2022

**Medrick FZE** | Tehran, Iran (Contract)

• Develop game base on design

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Aug 2020 - Jan 2022

**Dadeh Gostar Adak** | Tehran, Iran (Full-time)

• I was working as a front-end developer at adak company. During this time I have implemented the web applications as well as the pwa, and also i've gained experience on the server side

## ANDROID DEVELOPER

May 2019 -Aug 2019

**Awans** | Tehran, Iran (Internship)

• Awans was an insurance startup that i implemented the android application for them

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor's degree

Sep 2018 - Present

**Iran University of Science and Technology** | Tehran, Iran

• Computer EngineeringBachelor's degree

# High School Diploma, Mathematic

2013 - 2017

**AE High School** | Tehran, Iran (Grade: 3.91/4)